This website requires JavaScript.

Privacy Policy
==============

Search

Sign in

New Customer? Start Here

Order history

File Manager

Parts Manager

My Messages

My Coupons

My Account

Sign in

JLCPCB Help Center

Privacy Policy

Effective Date: March 26, 2024

Welcome to JLCPCB!

This Privacy Policy **(“Policy”**) applies to personal information collected through our products, related websites, other online services and your use of all services of jlcpcb.com as a user and other services which include a link to this Policy (e.g. customer support) (collectively, the "**Services**"). This Policy also summarizes when and how your personal information is collected, used, safeguarded and disclosed in connection with your use of the Services. It also describes your rights and available choices regarding your personal information.

**Data Controller: JiaLiChuang (HongKong) Co., Limited** (**"we", “us”, or “our”**) is the controller  (or similar term under applicable laws) of any information processed in connection with this Policy.

It is our policy to comply with applicable data protection laws. By using our Services and providing us with information, you consent to the storing, transferring and processing of your information in the manner described in this Policy. If you are under 16 or otherwise regarded as a child in your jurisdiction, do not provide any personal information to us without consent given or authorised by the holder of parental responsibility.

### I. **What personal information we collect**

1\. **Account Registration**

When you register an account with JLCPCB, we need to collect your IP address, username,email address and a password to complete the account registration. JLCPCB maintains your username,email address and password (in an encrypted format) inside our secure environment and only uses your information to welcome you back upon your return and personalize your experience on our Services.

2\. **Profile**

In order to provide you with better customer service, you can edit your profile and choose to provide us your account type, company name, industry, job title, account email, password, address book and sales tax certificates.

3\. **Delivery**

We need to collect your mobile phone number, consignee name, contact information, postal code, delivery address and bill address, to ensure correct delivery of goods.

4\. **Live Chat and Order**

When you chat online with your account manager or place the order, we will need to collect the texts, images, audios, videos, gerber files and 3D files you upload.

5. **Payment and Purchase**

**If you make any purchases from the Services, we will need to process your payment and purchase information. The exact personal information collected and used will vary depending on the payment method.** It will include information such as: User ID and details of your purchase and payment history.

6\. **Promotions, Competitions, Surveys and Event Information**

When you take part in any of our promotions, competitions, surveys or questionnaires about JLCPCB's services, or you engage with us through social media, you may provide information to us, or we may receive information about you, such as name, contact details (including address, phone or email), details of the emails and other digital communications (including any links in them that you access and whether you have opened the communications), your feedback and contributions to customer surveys and questionnaires, and any information specific to the event.

We will send you relevant offers and news about our products and services in a number of ways including by email, but only if you have previously agreed to receive these marketing communications. When you register with us we will ask if you would like to receive marketing communications, and you can change your marketing choices at anytime online, by clicking the unsubscribe link in the footer of any marketing email, over the phone or in writing.

7\. **Research, analysis and development activities**

We, or authorized third parties, automatically collect certain information from you when you use the Services to conduct research, analysis and development activities (including, but not limited to, data analysis, surveys, product and Services development and/or profiling), to analyse how you use our Services, to improve our Services or products and/or to enhance your customer experience, even if you do not have an account. See below for more details:

(1) Device information: We will, based on your specific operation during your visit and / or use, receive and record the relevant information of the device you use (including device id, operating system version, IP address, device brand, model, settings, environment, system parameters, device status, and other software and hardware feature information), device identification code (MAC/Android ID/IDFA/IDFV/OPENUDID/GUID/IMSI/Google ad id and Google Service framework id), network status information, WIFI information and device location information.

(2) Usage Information: when you use the Services, we will automatically collect information about your activity on the Services, for instance how you use them (e.g., date and time you logged in, features you’ve been using, searches, clicks).

8\. **Contact Customer Services**

You can contact us and give feedback by email, phone, and our social media (like ouer facebook, twitter, instagram, youtube, linkedin) or contacting customer service online. And when you are contacting us, you may provide your name, email address, company name, subject and your request detail so that we can give you a reply quickly and accurately.

In addition, you can ask your questions or find the answers you want in the Q&A section. It is important to note that the question you submit publicly may contain personal information even sensitive personal information about you or others, such as when you submit a question with an image that contains personal information. If you ask a question that involves the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person's consent before posting.

We may improve the Services based on your feedback, and publish it online or offline to facilitate our business and services. We will obtain your consent before publishing.

Meanwhile, we will conduct customer surveys from time to time. We hope that you will offer suggestions for the Services. We may collect such information including your name, user name, email, and answers to questions.

**If you choose to use other services not covered by the foregoing terms, for which we need to collect your information, we will seek your prior consent. We will use, store, disclose and protect your information in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy and the corresponding Terms & Conditions. Your refusal to provide the aforesaid information may prevent you from using a particular or part of the Services, but it will not affect your use of other services provided by us.**

### II. **Cookies and other similar technologies**

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device (computer, tablet, phone, or similar device) by us to ensure that the Service's normal operation and your convenient access to it. Cookies usually contain identifiers, site names, and some numbers and characters. Our websites, online services, interactive applications, email and other services may use Cookies and other similar technologies.

We send you Cookies in order to determine your identity and login status and to simplify repeat logins; we also save your preferences and personal settings, such as language, font size, shopping cart and other browsing preferences on your device.

We also use web beacons in the emails we send on your behalf. These web beacons track certain behavior such as whether the email sent through the Services was delivered and opened and whether links within the email were clicked. They also allow us to collect information such as the recipient's IP address, browser, email client type and other similar details. We use this information to measure the performance of your email campaigns, and to provide analytical information and enhance the effectiveness of our Services.

In addition, we and our partners use cookies or similar tracking technologies to better understand how and how often you use the Services, to improve the quality of the Services and optimise the user experience, and to deliver more relevant advertisements to you.

We will not use cookies for any purpose other than those stated in this Policy.  For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit our [Cookie Notice](https://jlcpcb.com/help/article/133-JLCPCB-Cookie-Notice).

### III. **Legal Basis And How We Use Your Personal Information**

We may only use your information when we have justifications (each called a "legal basis") under data protection law. To process your information as described in this Privacy Policy, we rely on the following legal basis which involve contractual necessity, legitimate interests, consent, compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

1\. **Contractual necessity**

(1) To administer your account and provide our services to you;

(2) To process your orders and deliver the products and services that you have ordered;

(3) To understand, diagnose, troubleshoot, and fix issues with the Services;

(4) To communicate with you in relation to JLCPCB Services and fulfill your requests via different channels(e.g., by phone, email, chat);

(5) To detect and prevent fraud, including fraudulent payments and fraudulent use of the Services;

2\. **Legitimate interests**

(1) To improve the Services and develop new features;

(2) To conduct research, analysis and development activities;

(3) To conduct customer surveys;

(4) To send you advertisements about products, services, offers, promotions, and events we believe may be of interest to you;

(5) To comply with a legal obligation to which we might be subject to, for example, we will process your device and usage information to comply with the legal obligation of ensuring the appropriate security.

3\. **Consent**

If you choose to provide us with information that may be considered “special” or “sensitive” in certain jurisdictions, you’re consenting to our processing of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

4\. **Compliance with applicable laws and regulations**

(1) To comply with legal requirements;

(2) To assist law enforcement.

### IV. **How We Share Your Personal Information**

In order to provide you with timely service, your personal information may be shared with our affiliated companies. For example, EasyEDA, JLCPCB and LCSC are affiliated companies. If you register or order products at JLCPCB.com, we will share the information about you and your order with EasyEDA and LCSC, who may contact you to inquire about the use of your component orders. We will only share your information within our affiliated companies for legitimate and explicit purposes, and only share the information necessary to provide the Services, and are bound by the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy. If a purpose concerned is not included in this Privacy Policy, we will state it in the corresponding notice of the specific services.

We may share the necessary personal information with authorized third-party partners (including technical service providers, data storage service providers, after-sales service providers, marketing promotion service providers, third-party SDK service providers, etc.) for the performance of certain features or to provide you with better service and a better user experience.

In order to provide evaluation, analysis or other lawful business services, we may also share your aggregated, de-identified or other anonymous data records with third parties. For example, we may use aggregated data to help partners (e.g., advertising service providers) understand the effectiveness, feedback and usage trends of their services.

In the event of a merger, acquisition or bankruptcy liquidation, asset transfer and other related transaction, if a personal information transfer is involved, we will require the new entity or organization holding your personal information to continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy through an agreement or other appropriate measures, and we will require such subject to take confidentiality and security measures of a degree no less than the requirements of this Privacy Policy to process personal information.

### V. **Cross-Border Data Transfers**

Currently, JLCPCB will store your personal information on a server located in Frankfurt, Germany.

For the purposes described in this Policy, and to the extent permitted by applicable local laws and regulations and with your authorized consent, we may transfer your personal information to the resources or servers for storage or processing, we may also transfer your personal information to third-party service providers and business partners and your data may therefore also be transmitted to other countries or regions. The privacy protection laws of these countries or regions may be different, and the jurisdiction in which these global resources or servers are located may or may not protect personal information to the same standards as in your jurisdiction. However, we will still strive to comply with this Policy to protect your personal information, and we will follow the legal requirements of the country or region where the personal information is located to carry out the corresponding cross-border transfer and other processing of personal information.

Where we transfer personal information outside of your jurisdiction, whether it transferred to our affiliates or third-party service providers, we will comply with relevant applicable laws. We will take appropriate security measures and safeguards to make sure that all such transfers meet the requirements of applicable local data protection laws. If you want more information relating to the security measures and safeguards, please contact us.

### VI. **Your Rights**

Privacy laws applicable in your country may give you the following rights:

1) **Right to be informed:** what personal information an organization is processing and why (we provide this information to you in this Privacy Policy).

2) **Right of access:** you can request a copy of your data.

3) **Right of rectification:** if the data held is inaccurate, you have the right to have it corrected.

4) **Right to erasure:** you have the right to have your data deleted in certain circumstances.

5) **Right to restrict processing:** in limited circumstances, you have the right to request that processing is stopped but the data retained.

6) **Right to data portability:** you can request a copy of certain data in a machine-readable form that can be transferred to another provider.

7) **Right to object:** in certain circumstances (including where data is processed on the basis of legitimate interests or for the purposes of marketing) you may object to that processing.

8) **Rights related to automated decision-making including profiling:** there are several rights in this area where processing carried out on a solely automated basis results in a decision which has legal or significant effects for the individual. In these circumstances your rights include the right to ensure that there is human intervention in the decision-making process.

The particular rights which are applicable to you (which might include other rights not listed above) may vary depending on your country. You should make yourself aware of the rights you have under applicable privacy laws in your country.

You can access and edit most of your profile information by signing into JLCPCB, and if you want to exercise any of your rights listed above, you can also contact our Data Protection Officer. For your protection and the protection of all of our users, we may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity before we can answer the above requests.

If you feel we have not resolved your concern, you have the right to lodge a complaint with your local privacy or data protection regulator.

### VII. **Protection of Personal Information**

JLCPCB takes the security of your personal information very seriously. We protect all data generated by and provided to us by our users from being stolen, compromised, or used in violation with this policy. We ensure that users' information is only used for providing service for users.

We promise to take the following responsibilities for protecting users' information:

· We work to protect the security of your personal information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.

· We use third-party payment processors that are fully PCI-DSS compliant to ensure that your payment data is handled securely.

· We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to guard and prevent misuse of your personal information. Our security measures include industry-standard physical, technical and administrative measures to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your information, to maintain data accuracy, to ensure the appropriate use of information, and otherwise safeguard your personal information. We restrict access to your non-public personal information to those employees and third parties who need such information to provide products or Services.

For more information about how we protect your personal information, including data privacy and protection, access restriction and control, payment security, incident response and so on, you can visit our [Security Policy](https://jlcpcb.com/aboutUs/security).

You should be aware, however, that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is completely secure. While security cannot be guaranteed, we strive to protect the security of your information and are constantly reviewing and enhancing our information security measures. You are also advised to exercise caution with respect to the sharing of your personal data and your authentication / security details (such as passwords, credit card details, transaction details) outside of our Platform / Services.

### VIII. **Your Choices & Controls**

You have the right to access, correct and transfer your data, limit its processing, object to its processing, or withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing that was already performed on the basis of consent prior to its withdrawal (if the processing is consent-based).

Moreover, should you decide that our processing breaches the provisions of GDPR, you have the right to submit a complaint to a data protection authority.

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data, we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such information, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain.

### IX. **Third Party Tracking and Online Advertising**

We use Google Analytics to recognize you and link the devices you use when you visit JLCPCB.com, log in to your account on our service, or otherwise engage with us. Google Analytics allows us to better understand how our users interact with our services and to tailor our advertisements and content to you. For information on how Google Analytics collects and processes data, as well as how you can control information sent to Google, review Google's site “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” located at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. You can learn about Google Analytics’ currently available opt-outs, including the Google Analytics Browser Add\-On here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

We may also utilize certain forms of display advertising and other advanced features, such as  Google AdSense, Tiktok, Facebook and Bing. These features enable us to use first-party cookies and third-party cookies(such as the Google AdSense advertising cookie) or other third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and display ads based on your past visits to our services. You may control your advertising preferences or opt-out of certain advertising products by visiting the ads preferences manager, such as https://google.com/ads/preferences, or by visiting NAI’s online resources at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

### X. **Children's Privacy**

Our products, websites and services are primarily aimed at adults.You may only use the Services if you are old enough to consent (by yourself and not by a parent or guardian) to share your data under applicable law. For example, you must be 13 years or older under United States law, or 16 years or older under European Union law. Otherwise, you must get permission from a parent or legal guardian to create an account on JLCPCB and use the Services, and that parent or legal guardian must agree to the terms of this Agreement. If you do not know whether you are eligible, or do not understand this section, please do not create an account until you have asked your parent or legal guardian for help.

If you are under 16 or otherwise regarded as a child in your jurisdiction, do not provide any personal information without your parent’s or guardian’s permission.

If the guardian needs to access or delete the personal data of the child at any time, please contact us according to Chapter 8 "Contact Us".

### XI. **Retention**

You may also cancel your JLCPCB account at any time by yourself via: JLCPCB website - Account Settings - Advanced Setting - Delete Account, or you can send an email to support@jlcpcb.com. When you submit account deletion, we take reasonable efforts to respond to your request. Once we have verified your user identity, we will delete your personal information from our systems timely. We will also delete personal information that relates to the in-app messaging function. Please note that messages sent to other users of our service are stored on their devices and cannot be deleted by us.

We keep your personal information only as long as we are either required or permitted to by law or as relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. That is, we will destroy or anonymize your personal data when we have reasonably determined that (i) the purpose for which that personal data was collected is no longer being served by the retention of such personal data; (ii) retention is no longer necessary for any legal or business purposes; and (iii) no other legitimate interests warrant further retention of such personal data.

In each case, there are also occasions where we may need to keep your data for longer in accordance with this Privacy Policy,our legal obligations or where it is necessary for legal claims.  Subject to applicable law, we may securely dispose of your personal data without prior notice to you.

After you have terminated your use of JLCPCB, we store your information in an aggregated and anonymised format.

#### XII. **Changes to this Policy**

We update this Policy in our discretion at any time by posting the amended version here or by providing such notice about or obtaining consent to changes as may be required by applicable law. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

### XIII. **Contact Us**

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy or practices of personal information protection, please contact us via:

Our Data Protection Officer Email: privacyjlcpcb.com

Mailing address : Unit 21 on 28th Floor, Metropole Square, No.2 On Yiu Street, Shatin, New Territories, HONG KONG, China.

We will review your requests as soon as possible and respond to you after verifying your user identity. If your request involves any complicated or significant issue, we may ask you for more information.

Last updated on Mar 26, 2024

* Company

* Support

* NETWORK SITES

Connect with us

© 2024 JLCPCB.COM All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://jlcpcb.com/help/article/Privacy-Policy) [Terms & Conditions](https://jlcpcb.com/help/article/30-Terms-%26-Conditions)

JLCPCB

  Welcome back, may I help you?
